SINEM CELENK

MBA | Marketing Professional
Vancouver, BC Canada

HELLO

Enjoys doing market research and finding new market opportunities. Interested in crisis management. Has an eye for good design. Stress resilient, good listener and has excellent observation skills. Has broad creative experience with multiple brands such as L'Oréal Paris, Garnier, Kleenex, Huggies, Enterprise, RE/MAX.

CONTACT

Mail: celenksinem@gmail.com

Web Site: sinem.space

VOLUNTEERING AFFILIATED ASSOCIATIONS & FOUNDATIONS

Vancouver General Hospital Information
Desk Volunteer (VGH) - June 2019 - June 2020

Vancouver International Jazz Festival
Environment Team - July 2017

Vancouver Opera Festival Box Office & Information Desk - May 2017

Children in Need of Protection)

TOHUM Autism Foundation Turkey

References available upon request.

EXPERIENCE

Sparktank Franchise Marketing Vancouver

Marketing Project Manager / June 2021 - Current

Managing digital local and franchise recruitment campaigns. Coordinating the work distribution. Working together with clients to reach the best results. Designing the company's creative assets.

COS Vancouver Part-Time Sales Advisor / Nov 2019 – June 2021 Delivered an exceptional customer service experience, resolved issues, and shared benefits of additional services. Recognized for being positive, intuitive, and client-centric.

Teskilat ICOM Advertising Agency Istanbul *Marketing Specialist / May 2018 - Oct 2018*

Managed digital and conventional advertising campaigns for global car rental company. Organized workflow to meet team goals and deadlines. Managed team and client meetings, overall campaign and event budgets. Analyzed research data.

A.N.D.B.R.A.N.D Advertising Agency / Istanbul Marketing Specialist / Nov 2017 - May 2018

Managed advertising campaigns for banking industry (Halkbank), gas, and technology companies. Organized internal and external meetings, managed budgets, analyzed data.

PR Specialist / Feb 2015 - Nov 2016

Developed corporate communications and PR Campaigns for FMCG and local brands. Organized launch parties, conferences and concept events for press and influencers.

EDUCATION

University Canada West / Master of Business Administration (MBA) (2020 – 2021)

Istanbul University / Bachelor's degree of Public Relations and Advertising 3.15/4 (2010 – 2014)

ISS Language and Career College of BC / Professional
Communication and Marketing Diploma Program with CO-OP
(2019 – 2020)

ISS Language and Career College of BC / Business Diploma
Program (May 2017 – July 2017)

EXPERTISE

Marketing
Event, Organization Planning
PR & Advertising
Customer Relationship Management
Preparation and Implementation
Research

Project Management
Budget Planning
Sales
Digital Communication
Crisis Communication
Data analysis